skyfire.com 2012-11-19

# Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment to Your Privacy:

  * Skyfire maintains strict privacy policies. The Skyfire application does NOT collect nor store Personal Information such as name, address, telephone number, or email address. We will not sell or transfer any personal information.
  * Videos via Skyfire's toolbar are mobile-optimized on your behalf, in order to provide you smoother play and faster starts, while still making video as crisp as your wireless connection allows. Skyfire processes these videos on its servers into optimal formats for your screen and bandwidth conditions. 
    * As a side benefit, adapting videos for mobile use helps you save battery, and if you are on a limited or capped data plan, this will save you money too!
    * In order to identify if there is a video where Skyfire can help, the application transmits URL information as you browse to Skyfire servers. The process is anonymous.
  * The SkyBar™ toolbar allows you a variety of social sharing and discovery features. If you log into the Facebook button, for instance, the toolbar will automatically give you a 'Popular' button that will suggest pages on any website that your friends have liked. Skyfire does not require that a user login to Facebook, nor any other social network to enjoy browsing. 
    * In order to process your requests, the application communicates webpage URLs and searches as you browse to our cloud service. This information is not stored in any way that connects to a named individual, only by an anonymous random ID number. The application learns your interests in an anonymous way, which can be used to enhance automated content recommendations, and serve relevant advertising. You will not see more ads because of this relevance technology.
  * For more information, please see the full Terms of Use and Privacy Policy below.

### Privacy Policy  
Effective April 6, 2011 

Your privacy is extremely important to us at Skyfire Labs, Inc. ("Skyfire", "we", or "us"). We respect the privacy of our users and seek to meet or exceed industry-best practices to protect your privacy, including supporting the Internet Advertising Bureau and Better Business Bureau joint self-regulatory principles. Accordingly, we have prepared this Privacy Policy for the Skyfire mobile browser, the SkyBar toolbar, our website, or other products and services we offer (collectively, our "Sites and Services"). By using any of our Sites and Services, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### 1\. What Information Does Skyfire Collect and for What Purposes?

The Skyfire Browser and other Skyfire mobile apps do NOT collect or store information that can be used to identify you personally such as your name, address, telephone number, or email address ("Personal Information"). Skyfire will not collect Personal Information without your consent. If you sign up for our optional free email newsletter via our Website, we do retain your email and other information you provide, but that is not linked in any way to your use of the Skyfire browser or other products.

Skyfire uses a completely anonymous user ID to identify specific Skyfire mobile browsers, which is not linked to any Personal Information. To the extent that our Sites and Services access your Device ID, Skyfire uses this Device ID to create a proprietary anonymous ID number that cannot be traced nor reverse-engineered to your particular Device ID or your identity. 

In order to process browsing and video requests, Skyfire has to collect certain basic browsing information, limited to Non-Personal Information, including the following:

  * When using the Skyfire mobile browser and the SkyBar toolbar, Skyfire automatically records certain information, such as website pages visited, searches made, phone model, and operating system version. This information is required to identify when there is a video for optimization via Skyfire's servers, and is used for studying aggregate user behavior, and to improve our Sites and Services.
  * A key feature of Skyfire's browser is its ability to optimize videos for viewing on your mobile device. When you visit a web page that includes videos, and play videos via the Video button on the SkyBar, Skyfire's servers will intercept and transcode those videos on your behalf. This process is anonymous and not tied to any Personal Information. Skyfire's mobile browser records usage data, including your web request, web response, IP address, the date and time of your request, size of the communication, and cookies, as well as client-side data such as connect times, connect failures and video playback quality.
  * Note that no data is ever transmitted to our servers when users access secure (HTTPS) sites, such as commonly used in online banking or ecommerce checkout pages. 

When using the SkyBar toolbar, you may choose to login to third-party services using the shortcut toolbar buttons provided, such as Facebook, Twitter, or other third-party services. You may use the SkyBar toolbar without logging in to those services, and you may log out at any time. Skyfire does not collect or store your account information for third-party services. Skyfire maintains only an encrypted token ("OAuth," in technical speak) to indicate to these third parties that you are logged in to your account with their services.

When you visit and browse our website, Skyfire may set and access one or more cookies (which are text files containing alphanumeric identifiers that we send to your browser and are stored on your computer). We use cookies to store limited session-related information to improve our website experience and understand repeat visitor trends. If you would like, you may be able to change your browser settings to limit our use of cookies (however, some features of our Sites and Services may not function normally if you do so). Please review your web browser's "Help" file to learn the proper way to modify these settings. In addition, as with most websites, Skyfire automatically receives and logs information from your computer that your browser sends, such as IP address, browser type, and Skyfire cookie information, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, landing pages, and pages viewed.

Skyfire may display advertisements and offers in its Sites and Services, including in the SkyBar toolbar. Skyfire serves relevant ads using a completely automated and anonymous process that enables Skyfire to target ads based on interests and topics that surface in keyword analysis of browsed pages. No human will read the browser session in order to target such advertisements, and no personally identifiable information will be collected nor provided to advertisers as part of this Service. We may also contract with trusted partners to perform anonymous reporting and analytics to refine user interest profiles creates with this information. However, Skyfire stores and uses this data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual or device. 

We may in the future introduce new Sites or Services that require a separate registration and may ask you to provide Personal Information when using those distinct products. Please keep in mind that standards for what constitutes Personal Information may differ in other jurisdictions.

Skyfire may use, disclose, reproduce, license and distribute any comments, suggestions and feedback to Skyfire regarding the use of our Sites and Services.

### 2\. What Does This Privacy Policy Cover, and What Doesn’t It Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of information that we gather when you access or use our Sites and Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply: (a) to the practices of third party companies that we do not own or control, or to third party individuals that we do not employ or manage; and (b) to any information you provide to use when you call us, write to us, or communicate with us in any manner other than through our Sites and Services.

Please note that end user license agreements ("EULAs") governing the use of certain Sites or Services may contain provisions that pertain to the collection and use of your information and which supplement or vary from this Privacy Policy. If there is a conflict between a EULA and this Privacy Policy, the terms of such EULA shall apply.

### 3\. Can Minors Use the Sites and Services?

Skyfire does not knowingly collect or solicit information from anyone under the age of 18, and requires that users to be of age 18 or older to use our Sites and Services. If you do not meet these age requirements, please do not attempt to register for or use any of the Sites and Services, and do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. If we learn that we have collected personal information from anyone under the age of 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 18, please contact us at privacy@skyfire.com and we will promptly delete such information.

### 4\. How Does Skyfire Share Information?

Skyfire does not sell, rent or share your Personal Information with other companies as a matter of policy. However, we may disclose Personal Information and non-Personal Information under the following limited circumstances:

  * Skyfire may disclose any information necessary to court orders, subpoenas, or legal process, or enforceable governmental request, or to establish or defend against legal claims, or exercise our legal rights.
  * Skyfire may access, use, preserve or disclose information to detect, investigate, prevent, or address illegal activities, fraud, security or technical issues, or potential threats to the safety of any person, or violations of Skyfire terms of use, or to protect rights, property, or safety of Skyfire as required or permitted by law.
  * To provide information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons who work on behalf or with Skyfire under confidentiality agreements and in compliance with this Privacy Policy.
  * Skyfire may choose to buy or sell assets, and in these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if all or substantially all of Skyfire's assets were acquired, or in the event that Skyfire goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. Skyfire may disclose your information in connection any of the foregoing.  However, keep in mind that our strict privacy policies with regard to the way user information is collected would inherently limit disclosure, since much of the information we collect is not tied to a particular user or device.
  * We notify you and obtain your consent in advance.

Skyfire discloses aggregate, anonymous log file and usage information in reports to third parties to assist those parties in understanding the usage patterns and performance results of certain advertisements, content, services, promotions, or features. For example, we may provide aggregate-level reports to an advertising partner for the purpose of showing delivery and performance statistics of a specific advertising campaign.

Skyfire utilizes certain third party services, such as Flurry Analytics, as a reporting tool in order to study aggregate usage patterns and improve our Sites and Services. Skyfire does not share Personal Information with such third parties.

If you have any questions regarding the management and use of personal information, please contact us at the address in the "Enforcement and Contact Information" section of this Privacy Policy.

### 5\. How Does Skyfire Protect Your Information?

Skyfire uses commercially-reasonable safeguards to protect the privacy of information collected under this Privacy Policy. Although we can not guarantee that such information may not be accessed or disclosed by breach of our safeguards, we seek to exceed industry privacy norms by not storing sensitive information and limiting the Personal Information we collect in the first place.

We limit access to information about Browser activity to Skyfire employees, contractors and agents who need to come into contact with that information to operate, develop or improve our products and services. These individuals are under confidentiality agreements and may face disciplinary charges, termination and/or criminal prosecution if they fail to meet their agreements. We review our data collection and use practices to ensure that we collect and use only necessary amount of personal information needed to operate, develop or improve our Sites and Services.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of any information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information. If Skyfire learns of a security breach, then we may attempt to notify you so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Skyfire also may post a notice on applicable portions of its Sites and Services if a security breach occurs.

The Skyfire website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site's privacy policy.

In addition, please note that information that we collect or that you submit may be transferred to, processed in, or held in countries (including the United States) other than the one in which you reside.

### 6\. What If We Change This Privacy Policy?

Skyfire may update this policy from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page. Each version of this Privacy Policy is identified by its effective date at the top of this document.

If we make a material change to this Privacy Policy that affects users of the Skyfire browser or other apps, we will post prominent notice within the applications and request new acceptance of the updated Privacy Policy before it applies to you.

### 7\. Who Can I Contact With Concerns Or Questions?

Skyfire regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. If you have questions, concerns or suggestions regarding this policy, please contact us at:

Skyfire Labs, Inc.  
Customer Care – Privacy Matters  
779 East Evelyn Ave  
Mountain View, CA 94041  

Note:  Some users may have more restrictive privacy policies based on specific country or wireless operator.  Please review the privacy policy available in the Skyfire application on your device if you are concerned.  The privacy policy can be found in the "settings" area in the Skyfire application.

|
